Dean, bro, you went back in the past.
Come on, bro.
Listen, I was so excited too, because I'm pretty sure
you play the trombone, and I'm out here playing
the sous-a-phone in my local.
You are?
Yeah.
Yeah, so.
Really?
Where are you in Tensee?
What is the band?
We're called the Knoxville Honkers and Bangers.
Our band is less than a year old.
We are a brand new.
The Providence version of the Honk Festival,
I was on the planning committee for like five years
in a row.
I was in a couple different bands.
The band called Extroder and Edition Band
in a band that's called Under-Tone.
Now used to be called What's Here.
I was in a couple of them.
I loved it.
This is my life for one chunk of my life.
And loved it.
It just got to make the t-shirt that year.
So I just wanted to show some people who might be there.
The person playing some bulls is in my band.
Some of these people, I think this is a player
that's like negatively taken from pictures of Honk.
Just like sketch.
But yeah, it was really, that was a big chapter in my life.
I don't know.
I already liked Pink and Red and Purple at that point.
So I was wondering where all you all played music.
What qualified someone as a community activist street band?
I think people have questions about that.
Like I've played like, I'm pretty sure
every played and abortion rights,
one of the bands played in abortion rights rally.
And I've definitely been with my bandmates
like going down to like where the prison is like in Rhode Island
and playing like outside so people could hear us.
And like I've done a lot of things like that.
But I think there definitely is within the community
like some split around like what does it really mean
to be activist.
I think some of them, they're,
that I think there are some bands
where like literally the only thing that they do
is play activist events.
And then I think under to a brass band,
we played like a regular show
but also would play activist events.
And then I think a story or an edition band
would play like more so.
I think mostly like community events.
I feel like mostly.
Yeah, I think people talked about it in the group.
Like are we doing enough to qualify
as like an activist rebound?